https://www.tne.co.uk/privacy-cookies-and-you/

Skip to contentMonday – Friday 7.30 AM – 4 PMT: 0114 251 3377hello@tne.co.ukFacebook page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowLinkedin page opens in new windowHOMEWEB DESIGNOUR WORKBLOGCONTACTYour PrivacyThe General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679Who we areOur website address is: https://www.tne.co.uk. Our company name is The Net Effect (WorldWide) Ltd. Registered in London Company No. 3152068; our registered office is 27 Nethermoor Drive, Killamarsh, Sheffield S21 1HR. Our telephone number is 0114 251 3377 and our usual working hours are 8.30am to 5pm.What personal data we collect and why we collect itWhen you contact us we collect the personal information you give us, such as your name, job title, company name, e-mail address, mobile and landline telephone numbers. With your permission, we may send you emails about our business, new services and other updates.How do we get your consent?When you provide us with personal information to enquire about our services or to complete a transaction, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.Personal data on emails and submitted contact forms on our website is retained for five years for customer service purposes but that information is not used for marketing purposes.Customer purchase records are retained for ten years.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting the Privacy Compliance Manager at: The Net Effect (WorldWide) Ltd., 27 Nethermoor Drive, Killamarsh, Sheffield S21 1HR, United Kingdom.DisclosureWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.CookiesCookie Consent Check Upon your first visit to our website, you will notice a subtle banner on the page alerting you to the fact that cookies are being placed onto your computer by our website. In order for our website to remember your choice of opting-in, we store a cookie called catAccCookies which expires after 30 days.Analytical Tracking Our website has Google Analytics installed which allows us to track and compile anonymous visitor statistics. The information collected ranges from simple traffic volume to the type of browser you are viewing our website with. This information is valuable to us not just for marketing analysis and quantification, but to improve the usability, security and load speed of our website content. Google Analytics is a popular, secure, flagship webmaster product from Google. The privacy and security of Google Analytics data is a high priority at Google that you can read more about on Google’s Analytics Data Safeguarding page. Google also offer a Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on that will allow you to automatically Opt-out of all websites that track your activity via Google Analytics. No personal information is collected by Google Analytics.Cookie nameCategoryExpiration Time_gaUsed to distinguish users2 years_gatThis cookie is used for throttling requests to Google Analytics1 minute_gidUsed to distinguish users24 hours We also use a cookie called devicePixelRatio which records your device’s pixel ratio to determine what resolution graphics should be served. This cookie has an expiration date of 7 days.SecurityTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.Amendments to this Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will update it on the web site, changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. Please view the policy on a regular basis, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.If our business is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell services to you.Questions and contact informationIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at The Net Effect (WorldWide) Ltd., 27 Nethermoor Drive, Killamarsh, Sheffield S21 1HR, United Kingdom.Links to other websitesThis privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. Go to Top
Consent to cookiesThis site uses cookies: Find out more.Yes, I understand
